const questions = [
    {
        question: "1303079343766331393",
        answer: "Joe Biden",
        answers: ["Joe Biden", "Donald Trump"]
    },
    {
        question: "1300840191771340801",
        answer: "Donald Trump",
        answers: ["Donald Trump", "Jo Jorgensen"]
    },
    {
        question: "1293638384913530880",
        answer: "Jo Jorgensen",
        answers: ["Donald Trump", "Jo Jorgensen"]
    },
    {
        question: "1303099476081553414",
        answer: "Howie Hawkins",
        answers: ["Howie Hawkins", "Joe Biden"]
    },
    {
        question: "1298621980665683971",
        answer: "Jo Jorgensen",
        answers: ["Jo Jorgensen","Howie Hawkins"]
    },
    {
        question: "1303305303249870854",
        answer: "Donald Trump",
        answers: ["Howie Hawkins", "Donald Trump"]
    },
    {
        question: "1303405858097901570",
        answer: "Howie Hawkins",
        answers: ["Howie Hawkins", "Donald Trump"]
    },
    {
        question: "1303056694360944640",
        answer: "Joe Biden",
        answers: ["Howie Hawkins", "Joe Biden"]
    },
    {
        question: "1303370008832155648",
        answer: "Joe Biden",
        answers: ["Jo Jorgensen", "Joe Biden"]
    },
    // 9 Questions so far, repeating below
    {
        question: "1303079343766331393",
        answer: "Joe Biden",
        answers: ["Joe Biden", "Donald Trump"]
    },
    {
        question: "1300840191771340801",
        answer: "Donald Trump",
        answers: ["Donald Trump", "Jo Jorgensen"]
    },
    {
        question: "1293638384913530880",
        answer: "Jo Jorgensen",
        answers: ["Donald Trump", "Jo Jorgensen"]
    },
    {
        question: "1303099476081553414",
        answer: "Howie Hawkins",
        answers: ["Howie Hawkins", "Joe Biden"]
    },
    {
        question: "1298621980665683971",
        answer: "Jo Jorgensen",
        answers: ["Jo Jorgensen","Howie Hawkins"]
    },
    {
        question: "1303305303249870854",
        answer: "Donald Trump",
        answers: ["Howie Hawkins", "Donald Trump"]
    },
    {
        question: "1303405858097901570",
        answer: "Howie Hawkins",
        answers: ["Howie Hawkins", "Donald Trump"]
    },
    {
        question: "1303056694360944640",
        answer: "Joe Biden",
        answers: ["Howie Hawkins", "Joe Biden"]
    },
    {
        question: "1303370008832155648",
        answer: "Joe Biden",
        answers: ["Jo Jorgensen", "Joe Biden"]
    },
    {
        question: "1303079343766331393",
        answer: "Joe Biden",
        answers: ["Joe Biden", "Donald Trump"]
    },
    {
        question: "1300840191771340801",
        answer: "Donald Trump",
        answers: ["Donald Trump", "Jo Jorgensen"]
    }
  ]
  export default questions;